Juan R. Ortiz

(347) 848-48543 juanortiz@outlook.com | GitHub

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Development Student with 10 years' experience in Electronic Engineering. Excellent communication skills and team player mentality able to provide different solutions to present issues. Ability to handle high pressure work bringing satisfactory outcomes to customers on time, and while maintaining strong attention-to-detail. Bilingual English & Spanish and Fluent in French.

Core Competencies:

- Object Oriented Programming
- Customer Service
- Smart Phone and Web Design
- Interpersonal Skills
- Troubleshooting
- Electronic Engineering

EDUCATION

Queens's Borough Community College, Queens NY

Course Work:

Web Technology

Creating Smart Apps

Web Client Programming

• C++

San Juan National University, San Juan, Argentina

Master Degree in Electronics Engineering

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C++ |JavaScript | HTML 5 | CSS3 | JQuery | Bootstrap

Frameworks/IDE: Atom | Notepad | Sublime

Software: Microsoft Suite

OS: Linux/Ubuntu | Windows 7, 10

Cert: CompTIA+

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Pier Sixty LLC, New York, NY 10011

April 2003 - Present

February 2018 – Present

Bartender

- Order and maintain inventory of bar products, including alcohol, drinks and supplies to ensure high volume of daily and weekly sales
- Ability to multi-task at a fast pace while dealing with various situations/individuals with over 1,000 customers weekly
- Interview/ Train new personnel

Atlantic Computer Services, Hoboken, New Jersey

1994-1999

Field Engineer

- Repair electronic devices such as monitors, printers, terminals and scanners
- Troubleshoot computers both Macintosh and PC compatible
- Assemble computers in large scale and design, repair and install networks
- Review design drawings specifications and customer requirements for newly engineered components and processes

INTERNATIONAL EXPERIENCE LVZ Informatics Company, San Juan, Argentina

1988-1993

Chief Engineer/ Manager

- Assist and guide the customer updated systems and electronic devices
- Collaborate with electrical and mechanical engineers to resolve product development and maintenance issues